♪ WE GO TOGETHER BETTER THAN
BIRDS OF A FEATHER YOU & ME ♪
♪ WE CHANGE THE WEATHER I'M
FEELIN' HEAT IN DECEMBER ♪
♪ WHEN YOU'RE ROUND ME I'VE
BEEN DANCING ON TOP OF CARS ♪
♪ AND STUMBLING OUT OF BARS I
FOLLOW YOU THROUGH THE DARK ♪
♪ CAN'T GET ENOUGH YOU'RE THE
MEDICINE AND THE PAIN ♪
♪ THE TATTOO INSIDE MY BRAIN AND
BABY YOU KNOW ITS OBVIOUS ♪
♪ I'M A SUCKER FOR YOU ♪
♪ SAY THE WORD AND I'LL GO
ANYWHERE BLINDLY ♪
♪ I'M A SUCKER FOR
YOU, YEAH ♪
♪ ANY ROAD YOU TAKE YOU
KNOW THAT YOU'LL FIND ME ♪
♪ I'M A SUCKER FOR
ALL THE SUBLIMINAL THINGS ♪
♪ NO ONE KNOWS ABOUT YOU (BOUT
U) ABOUT YOU (BOUT U) ♪
♪ AND YOU'RE MAKING THE
TYPICAL ME ♪
♪ BREAK MY TYPICAL RULES ITS
TRUE I'M A SUCKER FOR YOU, ♪
♪ YEA. DON'T COMPLICATE IT ♪
♪ CAUSE I KNOW YOU AND
YOU KNOW EVERYTHING ABOUT ME ♪
♪ I CAN'T REMEMBER ALL OF THE
NIGHTS I DON'T REMEMBER ♪
♪ WHEN YOU'RE 'ROUND ME ♪
♪ I'VE BEEN DANCING ON TOP OF
CARS AND STUMBLING OUT OF BARS ♪
♪ I FOLLOW YOU THROUGH THE DARK
CAN'T GET ENOUGH ♪
♪ YOU'RE THE MEDICINE AND THE
PAIN THE TATTOO INSIDE MY
BRAIN ♪
♪ AND BABY YOU KNOW ITS OBVIOUS
I'M A SUCKER FOR YOU ♪
♪ SAY THE WORD AND I'LL GO
ANYWHERE BLINDLY ♪
♪ I'M A SUCKER
FOR YOU. ♪
♪ YEAH ANY ROAD YOU TAKE
YOU KNOW THAT YOU'LL FIND ME ♪
♪ I'M A SUCKER FOR ALL THE
SUBLIMINAL THINGS ♪
♪ NO ONE KNOWS ABOUT YOU
(BOUT U) ABOUT YOU (BOUT U) ♪
♪ AND YOU'RE MAKING THE TYPICAL
ME BREAK MY TYPICAL RULES ♪
♪ ITS TRUE I'M A SUCKER
FOR YOU ♪
♪ [WHISTLE] ♪
♪ I'VE BEEN DANCING ON TOP OF
CARS AND STUMBLING OUT OF BARS ♪
♪ I FOLLOW YOU THROUGH THE DARK
CAN'T GET ENOUGH ♪
♪ YOU'RE THE MEDICINE AND THE
PAIN THE TATTOO INSIDE MY
BRAIN ♪
♪ AND BABY YOU KNOW ITS OBVIOUS
I'M A SUCKER FOR YOU ♪
♪ SAY THE WORD AND
I'LL GO ANYWHERE BLINDLY ♪
♪ I'M A SUCKER FOR YOU
YEAH ♪
♪ ANY ROAD YOU TAKE YOU KNOW
THAT YOU'LL FIND ME ♪
♪ I'M A SUCKER FOR
ALL THE SUBLIMINAL THINGS ♪
♪ NO ONE KNOWS ABOUT YOU (BOUT
U) ABOUT YOU (BOUT U) ♪
♪ AND YOU'RE MAKING THE TYPICAL
ME BREAK MY TYPICAL RULES ♪
♪ ITS TRUE
I'M A SUCKER FOR YOU ♪
♪ [WHISTLE] ♪
♪ I'M A SUCKER FOR YOU ♪