♪♪♪
♪ EVEN IF WE BOTH
BREAK DOWN TONIGHT ♪
♪ AND YOU SAY YOU HATE ME ♪
♪ AND WE GO TO BED ANGRY ♪
♪ I KNOW
EVERYTHING WILL BE ALRIGHT ♪
♪ I'LL BE HERE WAITING ♪
♪ I PROMISE I'M CHANGING ♪
♪ I JUST NEED ♪
♪ A LITTLE TIME TO
SHOW YOU I'M WORTH IT ♪
♪ I KNOW THAT I CAN
BE A DIFFICULT PERSON ♪
♪ I'M A STRESS CASE DRIVE YOU
UP THE WALL WHEN I'M WORKIN ♪
♪ ACTUALLY I'M PROLLY WORSE WHEN
I'M NOT YOU DON'T DESERVE IT ♪
♪ MAKE YOU NERVOUS CAUSE
YOU KNOW I'MA BREAK SOON ♪
♪ EVERY TIME I DO I SAY
SOMETHING THAT HURTS YOU ♪
♪ ACTIN LIKE I'M GONE, BUT
WE BOTH IN THE SAME ROOM ♪
♪ I DON'T LIKE TO BE WRONG
WHICH I KNOW YOU RELATE TO ♪
♪ AND I KNOW I MAKE
YOU FEEL LIKE YOU'RE
AT THE END OF YOUR ROAD ♪
♪ THAT'S WHEN I LOOK AT YOU AND
TELL YOU I'D BE BETTER ALONE ♪
♪ THAT'S JUST THE PRIDE TALKIN
ISN'T IT CAUSE BOTH OF US KNOW ♪
♪ I'M THE DEFINITION OF WRECK
IF YOU LOOK INTO MY SOUL ♪
♪ COMES OUT THE MOST ♪
♪ WHEN I FEEL I'M IN
A VULNERABLE PLACE ♪
♪ MADE A LOT MISTAKES ♪
♪ I WISH I KNEW HOW TO ERASE ♪
♪ WHEN I'M AFRAID ♪
♪ MIGHT GET DISTANT,
AND I PUSH YOU AWAY ♪
♪ BUT NO MATTER THE CASE ♪
♪ I'MA DO WHATEVER IT TAKES ♪
♪ EVEN IF WE BOTH
BREAK DOWN TONIGHT ♪
♪ AND YOU SAY YOU HATE ME ♪
♪ AND WE GO TO BED ANGRY ♪
♪ I KNOW
EVERYTHING WILL BE ALRIGHT ♪
♪ I'LL BE HERE WAITING ♪
♪ I PROMISE I'M CHANGING ♪
♪ I JUST NEED TIME ♪
♪ I, I NEED TIME ♪
♪ TIME, TIME ♪
♪ YEAH ♪
♪ WAY BEFORE I
BOUGHT YOU THE RING ♪
♪ WE WERE FIGHTIN
BACK AND FORTH LIKE YOU
WERE WEARING THE THING ♪
♪ TWO PASSIONATE PEOPLE NOT
AFRAID TO SAY WHAT THEY THINK ♪
♪ LEAD TO
PASSIONATE CONVERSATION
WHEN IT'S HARD TO AGREE ♪
♪ YOU KNOW ME WELL
SITTIN ON THE EDGE OF MY SEAT ♪
♪ LOOKIN AT LIFE OVER
ANALYZING EVERYTHING ♪
♪ ALWAYS DEPRESSED TRYIN TO
FIND A BETTER VERSION OF ME ♪
♪ SEARCHIN FOR
SOMETHIN I KNOWS PROLLY
RIGHT IN FRONT OF MY FEET ♪
♪ STUBBORN AS ME? ♪
♪ MAYBE NOT BUT
YOU'RE CLOSE TO IT ♪
♪ GOTTA A LOT OF ISSUES I'M
TRYING TO WORK THROUGH UM ♪
♪ GOING TO THERAPY FOR YOU'S
SOMETHIN THAT'S WORTH DOING ♪
♪ WHEN I KNOW YOU
BEEN THERE FOR ME THROUGH
ALL OF MY WORST MOMENTS ♪
♪ AND I KNOW IT
HURTS KNOWIN THAT I CARRY
THIS WEIGHT ON MY CHEST ♪
♪ MAKIN IT DIFFICULT FOR
ME TO OPEN UP AND CONNECT ♪
♪ A LOT OF REGRETS I APOLOGIZE
FOR ALL OF THE STRESS ♪
♪ THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT TO DO
YOU KNOW I LOVE YOU TO DEATH ♪
♪ EVEN IF WE BOTH
BREAK DOWN TONIGHT ♪
♪ AND YOU SAY YOU HATE ME ♪
♪ AND WE GO TO BED ANGRY ♪
♪ I KNOW
EVERYTHING WILL BE ALRIGHT ♪
♪ I'LL BE HERE WAITING ♪
♪ I PROMISE I'M CHANGING ♪
♪ I JUST NEED TIME ♪
♪ I, I NEED TIME ♪
♪ TIME, TIME ♪
♪ I JUST NEED TIME ♪
♪ I, I NEED TIME ♪
♪ TIME, TIME ♪
♪♪♪