♪ ♪
♪ HERE'S TO THE
ONES THAT WE GOT ♪
♪ CHEERS TO THE WISH
YOU WERE BUT YOU'RE NOT ♪
♪ CAUSE THE DRINKS BRING
BACK ALL THE MEMORIES ♪
♪ OF EVERYTHING
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH ♪
♪ TOAST TO THE
ONES HERE TODAY ♪
♪ TOAST TO THE ONES THAT
WE LOST ON THE WAY ♪
♪ CAUSE THE DRINKS BRING
BACK ALL THE MEMORIES ♪
♪ AND THE MEMORIES BRING BACK ♪
♪ MEMORIES BRING BACK YOU ♪
♪ THERE'S A TIME
THAT I REMEMBER ♪
♪ WHEN I DID NOT
KNOW NO PAIN ♪
♪ WHEN I BELIEVED
IN FOREVER ♪
♪ AND EVERYTHING
WOULD STAY THE SAME ♪
♪ NOW MY HEART
FEEL LIKE DECEMBER ♪
♪ WHEN SOMEBODY
SAY YOUR NAME ♪
♪ CAUSE I CAN'T
REACH OUT TO CALL YOU, ♪
♪ BUT I KNOW I
WILL ONE DAY ♪
♪ HEY ♪
♪ EVERYBODY HURTS SOMETIMES,
EVERYBODY HURTS SOMEDAY ♪
♪ EH EH ♪
♪ EVERYTHING WILL BE ALRIGHT,
GO ON RAISE A GLASS AND SAY ♪
♪ EH ♪
♪ HERE'S TO THE
ONES THAT WE GOT ♪
♪ CHEERS TO THE WISH
YOU HERE BUT YOU'RE NOT ♪
♪ CAUSE THE DRINKS BRING
BACK ALL THE MEMORIES ♪
♪ OF EVERYTHING
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH ♪
♪ TOAST TO THE
ONES HERE TODAY ♪
♪ TOAST TO THE ONES
THAT WE LOST ON THE WAY ♪
♪ CAUSE THE DRINKS BRING
BACK ALL THE MEMORIES ♪
♪ AND THE MEMORIES BRING BACK ♪
♪ MEMORIES BRING BACK YOU ♪
♪ DOO DO DO DOO ... ♪
♪ MEMORIES BRING BACK ♪
♪ MEMORIES BRING BACK YOU ♪
♪ THERE'S A TIME
THAT I REMEMBER ♪
♪ WHEN I NEVER FELT SO LOST ♪
♪ WHEN I FELT THAT ALL
THE HATRED WAS TOO
POWERFUL TO STOP ♪
♪ NOW MY HEART
FEEL LIKE AN EMBER ♪
♪ AND ITS LIGHTING
UP THE DARK ♪
♪ I'LL CARRY THESE
TORCHES FOR YA ♪
♪ THAT YOU KNOW
I'LL NEVER DROP ♪
♪ YEAH ♪
♪ EVERYBODY HURTS SOMETIMES,
EVERYBODY HURTS SOMEDAY ♪
♪ EH EH ♪
♪ EVERYTHING GOIN BE ALRIGHT,
GO ON RAISE A GLASS AND SAY ♪
♪ EH ♪
♪ HERE'S TO THE
ONES THAT WE GOT ♪
♪ CHEERS TO THE WISH YOU
WERE HERE BUT YOU'RE NOT ♪
♪ CAUSE THE DRINKS BRING
BACK ALL THE MEMORIES ♪
♪ OF EVERYTHING
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH ♪
♪ TOAST TO THE
ONES HERE TODAY ♪
♪ TOAST TO THE ONES
THAT WE LOST ON THE WAY ♪
♪ CAUSE THE DRINKS BRING
BACK ALL THE MEMORIES ♪
♪ AND THE MEMORIES BRING BACK ♪
♪ MEMORIES BRING BACK YOU ♪
♪ DOO DO DO DOO ... ♪
♪ MEMORIES BRING BACK ♪
♪ MEMORIES BRING BACK YOU ♪
♪ DOO DO DO DOO ... ♪
♪ MEMORIES BRING BACK ♪
♪ MEMORIES BRING BACK YOU ♪
♪ YEAH YEAH YEAH... ♪
♪ MEMORIES BRING BACK ♪
♪ MEMORIES BRING BACK YOU ♪